She returns like fog through a cracked front door Perfume on the air, but it smells like war
A pretty little promise with a poison Stitch soft hand sharp brin, old world witch
She finds the tender places, names them destiny It lights a little fire where your peace should be
She don't need a throne, she'll take a chair And everybody swear she was always there
Whispers in the hallway, candles in the mouth
that the threshold iron in my voice I don't get owned by another's choice name the lie watch it
thin watch it melt no crown survives the truth i've held panther beside me silent judge not cruel
not loud just won't budge she can hiss she can howl she can ring
but in particular, I'll send her mares.
Oh, excuse me.
I'm sorry.
I had a little sprocket in my throat.
Excuse me.
Oh my gosh, that was an accident.
That song wasn't about anybody.
Yeah, how are we doing?
Bedpan Man, Lace Perks, Jamie's Cowboys, Crystal Marie,
thing that is.
Anybody else?
That's we got a great crowd
Lenore tricks Lola Rudy. Yep. They're all here. I
Know I'm I feel like I'm looking extra beautiful tonight
Time what is this mask? I look like a retard still
Chris, I want to come back up. Can you hear me now? Oh, can you hear me now? Hey, can you hear me now?
Hey, it's Christine. It's Christine. Stakey's not making fun of my voice. I'm making fun of my voice.
I can laugh at you dying, almost dying on a big mac, but
it's not making fun of my voice or the heifer crew is gonna come bite you.
Christine that's terrible to say
Hey, psyche. It's weepy. Hi psyche. It's weepy
I'm so nice. I'm such a nice person. Why you mean to me psyche psyche
We the guests
Crystal
You hear me now
Yeah, yes
Oh my gosh, you fixed it.
I fixed it girl.
Yeah, we're here.
What the hell?
What was going on?
I don't know.
I think my microphone's having problems,
but did you hear Chris Christy was just here?
I didn't hear so why you say it? Why you say it? I didn't oh my gosh. He's trying to suck my
Christine stop trying to suck my blood Christine
Stop I'm not a vampire. I'm a nurse stop here making fun of me. Oh my gosh
You try to kill freaking everybody and
um that was wrecking in the car accidents in the movies in the movie it was in a it was in the
movie it was just a movie christine christine it's a joke it's just a movie we're just joking
in the movies i said in the movies in the movies because her name's actually not even christine
yeah you know we could say her name is
You know, and she named herself after, uh, a killer car, right?
You know, and then she named herself, I thought even her real name is her, and really not
Christine first of all.
But she told everybody that she named herself Christine after the killer car.
After the Stephen King movie, and that's what it was about, right?
Christine.
Yeah.
Get a life.
Exactly.
I said, Christine and Bita were naked around a tree, sacrificing babies and stuff.
It was a joke, because I meant the car, Christine, that Bita was driving.
Well, I said that she did that before that because she was trying to suck my blood
Right
I mean, he was literally going everywhere I went.
I didn't even know, she ruined all my friendships
with everybody that I ever had.
Oh, mine too, mine too, mine too, mine too.
And she was like sucking the blood out of like my veins,
like trying to suck my little body,
like my beautiful body.
How dare you, Christine?
Christine, leave Crystal alone, okay?
I'm sorry. Look at the chat is saying I'm sorry you had to deal with that crystal
You need a calendar with photos of crystal and psyche crystal. Do you want to do a calendar with me?
I can be my speedo and you can be in a bikini
That'd be a good calendar. I bet that would sell
Guys who would buy that calendar would have cost $100. We'd autograph it of course. I would not I did a calendar
one time and I did
Well a ballerina it was a one ballerina and then one crazy one which well
You were in a ballet outfit like a tutu
No, it was it was a for for France. It was it was a French
It was a French thingy. Can I give you like one of your French girls?
Kind of like that in a sense, you know, that's kind of and then I did totally opposite and I
was dressed as actual a snake and
I nobody wanted to be the snake and I was like, I'll be this okay. I'll be okay
Guess what guess what I got the cover
Listen I got the cover. Well, you're hotter than the Barker's beauties
I mean you should have the cover no I got the cover because I think I don't know
But nobody wanted to be that character and I was like
So okay with everything and like doing everything and like and I don't know if it was
I mean there was a way more beautiful women, but in and that shoot, but
Got it was a French ad. I'm gonna look at the midnight
I'm gonna look at the list right now. I can I haven't I'm in chat. She'd be too. I'm gonna say is midnight on the list
And you know, yeah, yeah, yeah, I I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Chris
I'm just talking to the chat one second, but I'm Crystal. Where have you been like are you having are you doing okay in life and?
everything going good
Yeah, I've just been focusing on my
family really and just
This is really negative
And I took the negative into a positive, you know, I'm like back where I used to be
You know, I used to like if I would get to like fucking if people would piss me off too much
Let's go into some kind of like kick, but let's do something fucking active
So we're not gonna like beat somebody's fucking face in you know what I mean, right?
And so that's where I'm at right now, so I don't want to beat Christine's face and I have to do
You know extra
You know or yeah, I think I'm pissed off big clips guys. I think I pissed off big clips today
So I don't have oh well. I like big clips
Do you want him to draw something like that of you?
No, but I'm sure they will
I mean, it's I haven't seen it in like five posts of me a couple of beta and I'm one of Sam and but I haven't
Like they I like bae. I love bae
Well, look, look is this be this is be this that's what beta looks like a praying mantis
That's Vita your friend Vita. You like the big one my friend dude. I try to be friends with her
It's faith Ferguson faith Ferguson. Do I know you hold on? I try to be friends with Vita. She was not nice to me for years
Oh, sorry guys
Hey, are you there? Hey?
But I like they are you there?
They have 10 seconds to say hello
Okay
I think it's I think it's a real person
Well, what is going on here?
They be careful hi
What is that fake that's fake
Okay, I don't want it. I don't think I can deal with that person right now. Yeah
Sounding the soundings like horrible. I don't I don't know it just didn't feel right. It's nothing felt wrong about yeah, that sounded
Super fake. I don't know what was going on. I'm so sorry
Me that you're a midnight. Are you midnight again on the list and we have more pictures?
Here's another one of beta or this is actually here's bay clips. That's a clip right there. Let's be bay clips
This is here's another one of beta
She looks great big smile, right?
Here's one of me and I guess I'm kissing Sam in this one. Do you think this one? Oh
You know I was kissing Sam in
You guys look amazing together. We're just wearing orange clothes. We're not it's not we're in prison
Here's another one of me. I think I was a little bit awake that night. How about that one?
Wow, they really, that was a lot.
That's a lot.
This one, how about this one?
But you know what?
Well, that's accurate.
How about this one?
Very accurate.
There's one of beta.
Can I have, is somebody, this one's accurate.
Of beta.
But listen.
I don't think so because it's not the skin tags they forgot the
What about me covered in vomit and and sores and you didn't say anything about that, but oh this beat it
Oh, she won't you say and beat it has skin tags. Okay, but this one is this one better
No, she doesn't have the skin tags, okay
How about this one
Accurate
Um, I think it's too wide too wide. Okay. Is that it? Oh, how about this one? Is this one a good one?
No, no, that's not good the big lips that you I think that was a fail for you on that one Crystal said I wasn't good
What the fuck was that? Well, yes, this is big lips. He's look how good he looked good looking he is
He is very cute. You're running the Alexander Mayer scarf
You know he's so funny he's got the little scarfie. I have a theory that he is Alexander Mayer's
I think big lips is but this oh look at the vegan Patriot looks great though. Oh
Yeah, she does. He's cute and
Let me see. There's a more who's this person. You know that guy and poor fucking
Who's that?
No, that's VP other direction. Okay, that's another VP. Okay, hold on
But that's your VP. That's your VP. You know people say I'm like the male vegan patriot
Did you know that? But I will say that I like I
you're like
Don't know why but you know that EP is like
It does like a lot of shit or whatever she doesn't do like a lot of shit to us. She's nice to me
I'm beat is like she's the only person I'm beat his panel to defend me and everyone's like
Turned against the kind of on her beat his panel. I didn't see I don't watch her. I don't watch Sam and and I like
Yeah, but yes. Oh pay Ferguson is back. Okay. Hold on. I'm sorry guys
I'm gonna put the banner up real quick pay Ferguson. Let's see. You should really like fucking hate on those fucking
Because they're not real dude. They're fucking
Not the fucking real people
Someone's saying I think they're saying I want candy
Is that Christine?
They're saying I want candy. I think I mean, but they didn't sound very good
I mean, is that better than Christine's?
Because she's the fucking one of those
Aaron Carter bitches.
It's Cristina's?
Yeah.
Didn't know that is she one of the disabled cuties. Yeah, she's a disabled. She's an older
She's not even the disabled cutie. He didn't even accept her as a disabled cutie
He was like retard cutie or old lady is called a retard cutie. Christine was yeah, there's retar Q
Yeah, we're like the old ladies
Christine Christine actually told me to jump off a bridge and she said she meant it
But then she said she was talking about bridge jumping, but then she said there are alligators in the water
Well, this is
My hand here. Yeah, you're like
Hey, hey, hold on I can do it too
No, I don't I can't do it. Okay. Okay. I can't do it, but hey Mason
I mean you in the chat. I love you Mason. You're cool. You see I want to come up and talk to crystal
They go away. You're not playing weird stuff. I don't know who you are topping the type of the chat. Tell me you are
Donate for a reading or something
But I don't like the picture of that cat and the cat looks demonically possessed and I heard some copyright music coming out of your
Um your thing so they get it together bitch really
Yeah, I'm just talking to the lady in the chat and she's so Christine
So she did want to see a little clip of like Christine and me talking about Christine and stuff
I can show you
She's like the devil's work, dude
Never work like because we have to respect our elders dude. I'm not so old
I mean so old man. We really I never but see I don't like it dude. It makes me feel so disgusting
Me too. I feel I feel it's so dirty even talking to that lady. I mean this yeah, I do
You don't even understand I cannot
I don't want to disrespect this old lady when she's just saying all these mean things about me.
Oh, she says horrible things. She says terrible things about everybody.
But look, do you want to see, okay, so I'm going to pull up. This is, um, have you ever heard of Osho?
Oh, no, I'll show you this one. I'll show you this one. You're gonna love this Christine Crystal watch this with me
Not sorry
Look at check out this out. I'll play a little bit of that. I'm gonna play the whole thing
I just want to get your opinion. This is what happened because you know, they had a beat I found a spider
She named the spider psyche and then she said we're having a secret spider ritual and psyche better watch
Oh spider
Another toilet and then they said it had nothing to do with me. Okay. I could do a crab. I could do a crab
Can I see you do what the crab walk? I want to see that. Can I can you do that crab walk?
You can you do the worm? Hey, okay, do you see this?
Look, do you recognize those women? I'm about to crab rock, but yeah, let's do this. Who are those
Why do I keep doing signs with my hands for the lady on the stream? I know these are just like
You see okay. I'm fine. Do you see these women on this on the screen? Yeah, I'm gonna play this I can't hear you
Yeah, watch this
I can't hear you it's okay. I'm gonna mute for some
What a crock you know Christine told her own son
Go jump off a bridge. And then she said
He was he did but it's been to like an alligator
First of all, why would she say that to her son second of all she said it why would she then say don't I
Mean but she did say jump off a bridge. Okay, Christine. I said sacrifice babies in the woods. You can tell me to uh jump off a bridge, okay?
But, you know, they're saying, oh, I was so drunk as a skunk.
Hey, first of all, really, oh, I don't really drink.
Beta, beta, you don't really drink.
Almost every time I hear you, you are so fucking drunk as a skunk.
I can't even barely hear your high-pitched Minnie Mouse voice.
How many wings have you built on the White Claw factory?
How many wings have they built?
How many cars do the executives of White Claw own,
just based on your monthly consumption?
And you're telling me,
I mean, that was a little bit ridiculous.
And why isn't anybody saying anything to her?
Oh, well, Bita, you're not only a drunk,
you're a mean drunk.
I mean, maybe I'm a sober, I mean, I'm kind of mean,
but yeah, you're a mean drunk, oh, shit.
I mean, James, that was lame.
I mean, okay, the yelling in the supermarket,
that was okay.
The bothering the lady at the Tempur-Pedic mattress store,
that was a little bit low.
I didn't like what he did at the fish counter either asking for a poop fish. That's really inappropriate
But then
The minute like he thinks it's his human right to come on my panel, right? He's like, oh my god
He wouldn't let me on his hand. Yeah, first of all, you're not an interesting guest. I mean, it's like you're just like so
pompous and like
I mean Tommy what do you think you're you know, but you're not Tom Cruise or I don't know Tommy Lee Jones or whatever
I don't know Tommy James. I think there's another guy in Tommy James a singer or something like that
You're not him. I heard you rap with Alexandra. It's terrible
shameful
Have you ever thought I'm just saying though and don't take this like too serious, but yeah, take it very light. Yes
Do you think honesty there might be a curse on you?
Well attempted, but I'm a better witch than they are so
Women are very powerful, you know, those those women are very powerful, but they have such bad intentions
It seems like I don't know this is this my
Interview and I might I might get a lot of hate this but whatever
To me, Vita and Christine is using you as like a ritual.
A ritual?
They're what?
They're using you.
You're pretty much the ritual, pretty much.
Well, you know, I know that, I mean, I did, I did like, um, like scry into the ether and
I saw them naked around a fire, like sacrificing babies and stuff, but I'm still more powerful.
Oh my god, oh my god, I was a joke Christina was a joke. It was a joke. It was a joke Christina was a joke
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry. He was it was a joke. I was about to tell you
No, it was not a joke like you don't joke like that
Oh my God, now I'm in trouble.
Get off, keep my name at your mouth, oh baby.
I don't talk to you.
Fuck you, bitch.
I don't talk about you.
Yeah, you do, yeah, you do.
I don't talk to you.
Fuck you, bitch.
Go suck six pussy.
How'd you know he had a pussy?
Stop talking about me, bitch.
I'm getting really tired of it.
You've done this before with Crystal,
and now you're doing it again.
It was a joke.
It was a dog.
Don't joke that way.
What I tell you, Psyche,
Way fuck go to sleep bitch. Why don't you go to sleep? It's time for me to wake up
I'm a productive
Drunk, I'm a productive adult
I'll be there drunk
You don't really nearly like you drink. Oh, she don't know
That's right. No, she doesn't
But psych I'm telling
Sike
I think I inscribed in the ether and see you dancing naked around a fire. Okay. It was a joke
Well, but you know something I'm getting real tired of it
Okay, that's me hey money, what's up you're on with crystal Murray
Money crystal
No shit, I forgot to meet myself. I'm high as fuck right now. What's up Tate? What's up Chris too?
Wow, can you believe that? I mean, you know her name is not even Christine and so all this. Oh my god
I mean it my job my job
She was just that was all bullshit. I forgot she named herself after the Stephen King
She just bought like seriously. She has been trolling me for fucking months
Okay, like about making me feel guilty about that. I'd say Christine does this and that
Crystal said this on our show. It's not a matter of fucking name. How is that doxing? How is that? Oh, oh, my job
Oh, they're gonna think I'm doing no one even knows who the fuck you are woman. Okay, you
Wrinkled old hag
Sike, he's don't say that about oh, I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry
Fucking wrinkled old hag
Yeah, let's see some more bikini pictures that are touched up by AI. Let's see him more, okay?
You don't look that good. You don't look like Bridget Bardot laying on the beach. You look like a wrinkled old hag
Okay, I'm sorry to say not sorry
You don't mean to kill myself. Honestly, you're in the you're on the list Christine
You told me to jump off a bridge and you meant to it's not about. Oh, oh, this is just bridge jumping for a sport
You meant it in a different way. I know you did you old hag. Okay?
fucking witch
Not you crystal. I'm talking about crystal or christen. Yeah, what do you think about you like that clip that funny clip?
Did you see that?
The dude from the suppose so spitting that she made me laugh that made you laugh
Yeah, when they spin they were spitting because it was so ridiculous and she's oh, she doesn't really be doesn't really drink that much I
Don't drink that much
I'm gonna get shit for this tomorrow. I know I know I know I know but what about a spider ritual and then they make fun of me
Oh, you forgive me for coming coming to your stream being very rude. You hear me Jaycee
Are you mad at me, JC? I didn't call you. The God he gave me a number. I called
Yeah, we hear you where she go. Oh, no, JC. I'm sorry if that was you that I think it was I think it was Amanda's house
I called actually I heard a boyfriend and a girlfriend arguing and I heard Amanda's voice
I think you have a tattoo on your back. I do too. Let's see
Thank you
What do you think money for 20
It's official, huh?
Thank you. I got tattoo all this, but you and Cali so yours
Here guys spider we can Sarah was here spider we can stare what that is
Well, they they're like psyche we consider except they're a spider and they give spider facts like for example
Do you know that we swallow 10 spiders a year in our sleep?
I heard that before.
For that before?
Yeah, I know, I know.
I'm trying to unhide midnight.
It says midnight returns or something like that
or midnight again or something.
I mean, it took me an hour to do a thing that is midnight.
Can you just talk on the ALT tonight
and then I'll do it tomorrow?
I'm a little too drunk to figure this out.
Am I here?
You are.
Hey, hey
Well, what do you hear your crystal or Christine and
Alexander my gosh, I want to change different streams
I hear you and I hear
Sorry guys
Can I like good tomorrow? I'll do it tomorrow. I think I'm sorry. Hey, but you're drunk
My gosh, can I tell midnight that I love midnight midnight Crystal loves you
My gosh, can I tell midnight that I love midnight?
Yeah, okay, it was was Christine it's like an echo of a chamber for mail
Why was Christine and Alexander McQueen seeing a duet of I want candy. Why did the gates of hell open when they did that?
Money
You want some more coke that's all that was that you didn't hear him singing. I want candy with Christine
Why would they do that or are they singing about that or are they saying that?
You know Aaron and I want candy that's actually for my coat. No, what is Christine sending these people? What did she send you?
These flying monkeys, I think she's like we can wish for the West honestly
Oh my gosh, I hear an echo. I'm gonna have to read there's a little bit might be a little echo
It's okay.
Yeah, thank you guys.
You did my other stream.
You're fine.
It's a little bit confusing.
But guys, Christine was saying, I want candy.
They're seeing together.
I want candy.
No, I can't deal with this.
It's okay.
Turn on the volume of something.
I think you're, I think you have the, you have the YouTube on some more, too.
You have the YouTube stream on.
I'll come right back.
Okay.
Just remember.
Yeah.
I'll be right back on.
I'm going to talk to the money for 24 hours.
Yeah, the echo is kind of driving me crazy, but I don't want to complain.
It's okay.
I don't complain.
Hey, Tricks.
Hey, Rudy.
You want to see Rudy?
You like my cat, Rudy?
What up, cat?
That's Rudy.
Come on, Rudy.
Boy, come on.
Give it up.
Yeah, that's meant to be cat, Rudy.
Hey, Rudy.
These are my cats. They're so they're so terribly abused
Christine said my cats hate me. You hate me Rudy. Do you hate me? Am I your best friend?
He looks like a happy cat, huh?
He's telling what you he's just chilling and tricks and sitting over there the north sitting there
Lola is probably sitting right around here, too
I mean, it's like my cats are my cats are all good. Christine. How dare you say my cats hate me?
Fawzi wrote me a letter and he says can I please move in with you?
This old lady makes me look peanut butter out of her twat
what
That's what Fawzi wrote in his letter. I don't know if it's true
Hey Christine I can make jokes too
And now I'll tell you I blame the panel on me because I'm probably gonna get blamed for something too
It's not even her fucking real name. Hey, her name is not even Christine
She just has a pseudonym from the Stephen King book. So whatever she says, it's not even her fucking name
She's anonymous person. That's her name to me
Debra Debra Connors or something like that. It's like someone's all she's just a big fake
I use my name and she tells my name. She has my name. She talks about my family
She talks about my neighbors. She talks about all the all this personal shit
And she's saying that it is real and then she's mad at me for using her Stephen King
Pseudonym in a joking way. She's a fucking troll. She's a bitch and a troll. Okay, bitch
Sorry, not sorry
I ain't got no problem with this thing. This thing cool people
She's not cool. She's not cool. You saw you saw the bikini photo. I know she looked in the bikini
You know that was actually Bridget Bargeau and then with her face with AI heavy AI making her look 30 years younger
At least or maybe 40 years younger. I think that picture was taken in 1956
honest
Honestly
You want to watch some more? Do you ever see me as Michael Jackson money for 20?
That I have a scene. You haven't seen that one. Okay. I have to show you that one. Yeah, it's only a few seconds long
It's only like 30 seconds long, but yeah
Here's me as Michael Jackson on the trip and trips up trip trip trip and trip trip kicks
Chip kick. Yeah, trip kick on rumble. I can't keep up with these people. Oh, that's why I need it. I'm confused, too
I'm confused, too. This is on a
Oh my god. Do you want to see me say the N word the other night on Bita's show?
I heard you. You crashed out. I heard about it.
I crashed out. Do you want to see that one? Okay. I'll put that on home.
Also, thing that is, you got also clipped on Rumble.
Thing that is, you were also fighting with Bita on Rumble.
But here we go. Share screen. I got it, guys.
Hold on. I got it. I got it.
Why am I
a long time without getting old my wife just turns the views and opinions expressed in this program are those of the speakers and do
Not necessarily reflect the views or positions of any entities they represent
Your discretion is advised clumsy over there talking the worst shit
I'm the worst shit about me in my in your chat talking about
Mom all that and then you're gonna be upset if somebody if I feel the spider that had nothing to do with you
I'm sorry, but if I knew that spider represented you I would get it an over and send it back to your area
You know
I didn't want it. I didn't know exactly what was going on
You're gonna fucking behave when you're on the fucking panel
Me they gotta focus be the be the I'm here be the we got a fuck. Yeah, I don't even know he has nothing to do with psyche
Okay, this is a manipulation tactic that this old lady likes to use. Yeah, okay
She likes to think that she's knows better. She's actually not
Not psychology worthy at all and not even at the lowest level of psychology. I promise you
Okay
But she's
Paid a lot of money, you know her parents paid a lot of money for her to
Do that and then all and then she made fake jewelry she makes like a plastic
You know, the fish, you know, fish-string, jewelry.
Yeah.
He sells fish-string jewelry.
Wearing like the fish.
Like, she's like, she's like some, some, some like,
like the fish, you know, the, you know, what they use to like.
Fish-string, yeah.
Like little babies make when they're,
when we're trying to do something for fun, you know,
that's what she is.
You know, P.A. makes really nice jewelry,
beat it, but you're saying beat it makes crap.
Yeah, it's, it's fish-string jewelry for children.
Okay.
Okay, well, but here I got a little bit excited on the show
I just want to play a little bit of this when I start saying the n-word and your discretion is advised
I'm saying that because she makes everybody else. I only
criticize her
Job because she likes to criticize everybody else's employment, right?
Right and it's good for the goose is good for the gander, right exactly and she's only doing it
But she's actually the worst like listen if I lived in Cali if I grew up in Cali and lived in Cali
I'd be a billionaire
billion billionaire
fucking guarantee
Not saying that I don't have a good amount saved, but I know billion or millionaire
Tell you that
Well, here we go. I mean, let me just play a little bit more of it. I'm not gonna play very much
But I don't live off daddy's money
Okay, I'm gonna play a little bit longer. The thing that is is Giggling is dumbass off. He says here we go. Here we go, guys
I'm having to talk once again, you know
Everyone speaks for themselves. I don't know why
and Christine is an old prostitute oh my god okay that lady is so old
She had to have I don't know when she ever existed in our area where she thought
It was okay for her to fucking talk to people the way that she does but around here
If you talk to people like that you get fucking shown the fuck up. It's a show me state. Okay show me respect
Yeah, you got to get shown up. Yeah, show me the money. That's what I have to say
We'll watch this a little bit more. Here we go
I knew, I know why you, but...
Yes.
Don't know why she's a liar
Where you're calling
You know
But why are you calling me a beach?
I guarantee you might be a is she's a preacher now, but she would rip out of that preacher suit and she would whoop some ass and
She would not and God would forgive her for it. Yeah
I don't know why I'm having so much fun with Capricorn.
We're gonna say a little bit more of the crystal and then I want you to talk one second.
Watch a little bit more. Watch a little bit more.
And that's how it works.
You don't fucking disrespect people and think that it's okay for people to just disrespect you.
No, Christine, I'm not. Please make that more specific when you say that.
Okay, you're gonna double down? Well, then I'm gonna triple down and I'm gonna fucking make it worse for you, bitch.
Right in my opinion. Sorry. Yeah, it's okay. He was watching a little bit more and then we can talk. Oh, I can't hear you
Okay, one second watch this
Well diving and like
Anybody fucking going in like
This can be taken out of context and like I don't want it like that. Okay, so like let me say this psych go to my channel
Go to my post and you'll see how fun bridge jumping is I can't hear it. So what am I?
What's on youtube?
I can't hear anything so
I won't let him on he put his gun in his mouth today. I'm not gonna put him on
You don't hear the video that's playing
Yeah, there's alligators you live in floor. We live in Florida. There's alligators in everybody of water
Pacific Ocean, you know that like surfers get you know attacked by sharks
I do I mean it's very rare for them to
Tell me seriously why a woman dedicated decades of her life away from her own family, her own
children, her own holidays to care for somebody else.
Show me the money.
Selflessly.
We're going to watch this a little bit more.
12, 14, 16 hours a day.
What about Tracy, why do you want to say that about me?
You know how many women that you just saved me and asked me about that were good people?
You don't even know me.
I don't even know. He has nothing to do with my children.
I'm not stalking anybody, please.
I mean you found my personal tiktok somehow. I don't know how you did that. What? Oh, oh my god
So mine just happened
He was on tiktok. Yeah, nobody really knows they don't use it so I don't
offhand one day just to check on some people and it says
Psyche Awakens has set up to you and I have a screenshot of it.
I'm just wondering how you found it. I'm honestly just curious.
So you think that it's linked to YouTube somehow?
Yeah, probably or something. I don't know.
Oh, okay.
Okay, no, no, you know why it's because people on YouTube or is anybody from YouTube subscribe to you because I'm subscribed to a lot of people on YouTube there
And maybe it's came okay
So you say you say you're joking and all this stuff is not that serious and sometimes you're playing and what what what what whatever
I want to know this. I want to know this because there's a lot of I get just I'm I mean
I'm just this is just one thing that came to my mind
What did you you know Tracy is a really good friend of mine and I care about her and I did meet her
You know, uh by coming on your panel and standing up
What was going on with you know, Michael? It was all about that. That's why me and Tracy met. Why did you mess with her and tell her you know that she's you know
Religious woman. She's a good woman. She works hard. She doesn't even she doesn't come around there because
Whatever for whatever reason why did you tell her I was satanic and to stay away from me?
Well, no, we're going back months and months. This is like six months ago. Well, it doesn't matter. You I just want to know
Why would you say that everything?
If you say things are a troll then why is that why do you go and actually go behind the scenes and say that to somebody?
Well, you did didn't you message her and told her I was satanic to stay away from me
I'll be back and then I got to take a phone call
Okay. Okay. You want to contact her and say, hey, Tracy, I miss you. I apologize. If anything, why do you have to throw me in the mix and call me that?
I don't remember the context of it.
You don't remember the context. She has them. She still has the messages. I saw it.
I can go back and look at it, but I don't remember exactly why.
I would never forget that.
I know. Well, I am forgetful.
Hi, Erin.
Wow. Well, that's the thing. You know, I'm not an atheist, by the way. I'm not. I think atheism is...
Uh, no, I'm talking about IP to runway. I'm not an atheist
right
One minute. Oh
I think you're muted
Oh, I was looking at my TVs on delay
Nevermind
I mean, is it, are you, are you going to go live and just like, you know, obsess about
what everybody else says are minimal and make it live, right, I'm not going to go, no, I
mean, you can do whatever you want.
I mean, you want to do, do that.
You can do whatever you want.
But I mean, like, my tonight, but it was a really like weird night last night and it's
like, okay, okay.
Well, no, I mean, you promised that he says like, good, did you think Tracy would feel
when you did that seance about my whole shit and shit like that? And she still says it. Okay.
And so and I, what do you mean? He treated him like crap. You don't know any.
Certain problems been stuff like that, but he wasn't a bad guy to me. He was always kind to me
So why are you trying were you trying to summon him if he was a bad guy? I didn't and I said he's not a bad guy
I said he what had his problem. So, you know, it's like I'm gonna go say not to be this nigga this
Is anybody perfect?
Why even summon?
I don't believe that.
That should have stuck to you.
Wow.
That I can take.
He's a Yu-Gi-Oh master.
Peter.
I summon.
No, this thing.
I don't even know what that means.
I don't know what summon.
You summon monsters.
We don't know that's Yu-Gi-Oh.
Yu-Gi-Oh.
I don't know.
Tracy had to find me something.
That's the weird thing.
Quick.
That's enough that's enough
That was a lot that was a lot. I'm sorry. I'm sorry guys. Hey, what's up guys wait crystal. Hold on
There we go
Hey
Clemsi her name's not even Christine her name's not even fucking Christine, right and she
It's not even fucking Christian. It's it's carton lady. What her name is it's carton lady psyche
Christine hi Christine you're on the air
What's up, Eric? I could Trina or something. Oh, oh
shit
Wait, what happened? No, I didn't hear that. I didn't hear that. Hey, what's up guys?
How are we all doing? We're here with Alexander McQueen. You're here to Alex too
Why are we saying I want candy with Christina and a duet and opening the gates of hell tonight?
I
Turned on money for 20s to have a laugh and then I hear
Money for 20 the loser just got an essential booking last night. He's a criminal
You like hanging out a criminal psych
Don't like it. I just which is weird my audience, but hey criminal has a fucking wrench on your panel
We're good thing that is in the cat like a loser. Haha
Katrina we should call her
Trina but
Your clumsy. Yes. You're lucky man. You're lucky buddy. What is going on? You lucky?
You know you look you you look me in a car and she's mad that I said and tell Sam and suck my dick
That's not real New York Sam is a pussy
I don't even believe it's from New York
That's a little pussy. I see you. I see you. I'm gonna get next to you right here
I'm gonna point out. Yes, my clothes comes in, you know teeth having fuck smile for me
You have a little finger. It's the fuck up. No waving. I go back
Come on
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come
Taco
By his little gay face, he puts a wig on and he becomes a woman
Well, I'm sorry don't know what you guys
Sorry to break you guys look at them
That's a transvestite
Yep
You're too loud
Fucking everything up dude that muta for a minute Alice crystals in on this story crystals tell us about clumsy
Okay, let me tell you clumsy used to harass the fuck out of me for a fucking years, dude
Like hard dude, he was like trying to harass my family, but then he realized my family was about to you know
like we're badass and then he stopped and
Then his teeth fell out. It's not a he comes. He's like 40 diamond in the skies at least 40 except it
And then his teeth fell out.
I'm just not transiting you.
I hear your teeth fall out at this age.
Your teeth fall out when you're like 90.
Where's the hold on, Alexander?
That's insane.
That means you've been stuck in meth or crack your whole life.
Crystal Moly, didn't you get all your teeth remote?
Nope.
Yeah, you did.
You want me to show you a picture?
No, that's not okay. Yeah, go ahead show a fake picture a fake picture by the way
You know what's more believable why don't you tell everyone about our relationship ten years ago when I was doing time in prison
Remember you you said me and you were writing each other remember
You remember? You went to go visit me. You used to bring me drugs and all that shit, remember?
I have no help.
I asked you to bring drugs one time, remember? That's what you said!
I never said that you're a fucking weirdo, dude.
You always make up weird shit.
You've always been obsessed with me.
I don't know your obsession.
Why?
Maybe it's because-
I'm sorry, mama.
I'm scared of you.
I have no idea.
Mama has no one.
It's fucking weird, dude.
I'm not a dude.
I'm sorry.
Rihanna Glow, why'd you put a gun in your mouth today
on my show?
You know what?
Christopher Marie.
Look.
Why would you do that through your glow?
Wife is there. Well, his wife is there. He put a gun in his mouth. I'm on the show
Listen
Can you guys shut up?
I'm important. I know I am
At least let me
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry
What's up, psych?
Can you hear me in the corner?
I'm not.
Are you okay, Christa Marie?
Yes, sir. I'm fine. I didn't know you were talking to me. I was talking to her.
Well, do you have big teeth in you? You talk like you don't have real teeth. You had like big teeth in you.
Yeah. You sound like you have baneers in your mouth.
It's not baneers. Well, they're dentures.
Well, you sound like you talk like you're bad.
Then why are you?
You don't turn your camera on you
In your mouth you sure about that. Yeah, you sound like you have no teeth
So, you know what that sounds like
Oh
300 was your boy. I'm so sorry Aaron. I thought it was your boy
Was my boy
Are you weird? What's going on?
And I said hello. Are you stupid Aaron? I'm sorry
Shit to both these bitches too
Sorry, I said hello
Okay
They're scared bro, they're scared of the smoke
Have Dina go after Crystal Marie
She's making me and she's making me and she's making me and she lost that Molly right now.
I can't do more. I can't you guys can't compete with me. Real shit. Oh, you're making me hungry.
You could show me what you want to show me, but I'd rather see some enchiladas that Molly
Dollar Tree background. She bought that shit at Dollar Tree. I this costs like three hundred dollars. Are you kidding me?
I bought that shit at Dollar Tree for one dollar
Huge I got that shit from T-Move for ninety-three cents
Twenty years ago for like three hundred dollars, okay, like 20 years
Like your government sweater you're wearing
Jesus
Royals
KC baby
It's okay. I still represent you need to go buy some skateboard clothes and look more gosh
Like you look like a
Play today, I represent KC baby all day go fucking die. Oh, yeah
Oh, yeah, in Minecraft in Minecraft Jesus Christ you see psyche
This is what you got on girls
I'm so sorry. Hey Closy. Hey Closy. I got to really get laid tonight.
There you go. Let's go do that. Erin say hello for me.
It's a couple of minutes, but Erin's not walking.
I'm doing it, bro. Just kidding, bro.
Erin's not walking.
He was talking crap about my shirt because it's going to be a royal shirt.
You know, you would look better without the shirt.
And that's that and we'll we'll be behind you like that's that. Yes
It's like ready to punch me right now, so look
Get him Dina
The first time she's been on camera hey, what's up nice to meet you. I'm not good actually a block or whatever your name is 300 glow
the
We don't want to see your ass right now
Oh look at my shit look at my plate of food
Go do that for your man who's gonna do that for their
My fish tacos and then we can have who's gonna do that for their man who?
I'll do it for you. I'll do it for
You don't want you to jack off right now in front of my kitty cat and pity my pussy. Don't jack off
Pussy by the way
That's what girls say
Oh my god.
Oh shit, that is a cat.
It's a real cat.
It is a real cat.
Four of them.
I thought you meant the leather pussy.
I don't have a leather pussy.
You're sick.
Something so sick.
Alright, I'm pretty sure.
Staying out.
He's almost sexual and he loves.
You know your friends dig has a pussy. That's all right. Don't be jealous crystal. Don't be jealous
Definitely not I love
Relationships I enjoy it. I think that psyche needs some
Friendships
Friendship you need somebody to suck them up. That's it. Well, who wants to do it?
I know you want to you know you want to
the
Magnum crystal crystal. I'll be okay. Show your make
That big-ass titty
You don't have
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry. Hey. Yeah, he's a dreamer
They're dreamers. Hey, I'll be one case short
Dream yeah, yeah, you should dream on buddy. So what? Oh, well, you're a old lady
It's crystal not Christine. Hey crystal, you know, you're old, right?
How old are you you're like my age and she's young. She's like you're
Christina's in her eighties and she was seeing I want candy tonight made me so
I'm not I didn't groom him
I just really know what's up with the streets. He has a wife. He's a wife. I'm really plugged in
Is he plugged in when he fucks
On the stream he did this you gotta let him do that on YouTube. He never fucked me on you. Where was this at?
What is this?
I'm on kick or whatever.
It's a rumble, rumble, rumble.
Where is that? I'm going to need to find that video.
That's Chris K. fighting.
That's not because we're on a blow.
That's because he's fighting a door.
You know, Chris K.
You know, they get a little crazy.
He's crazy.
He's mad.
Chris is going to fuck you but a guy.
Nobody wants to fuck you but a guy.
A man fucks you, you fuck your man, you fuck your man dude, you fuck your man buddy, you fuck your man, you don't fuck your wife, you fuck your man, you're fucking your man, oh my gosh, you fuck all the, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls, I've seen his balls,
As you fucking around with the fucking homosexual
No gay shaming, no gay shaming, can we, uh, expose with Chris K?
I have a respect, if you're thinking of me, his wife's gonna be there with the camera, okay?
except for coming like that you call me the n-word yeah you're fucking a nigger okay you're
off the show where's my mouse you're off the show the one disrespectful to your wife
out of here out of here you fuck other guys on stream on a daily you are fucking other guys on stream
Okay, I'm gonna end this dream. Oh, sorry. Yeah, that's like he was that too bad that was